const QuestionList = [
  {
    question: "1: Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
    optionA: "<javascript>",
    optionB: "<script>",
    optionC: "<scripting>",
    optionD: "<js>",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    question:
      "2: What is the correct JavaScript syntax to change the content of the HTML element? <p id='demo'>This is a demonstration.</p>",
    optionA: "document.getElementById('demo').innerHTML = 'Hello World';",
    optionB: "document.getElementsByName('p').innerHTML = 'Hello World';",
    optionC: "#demo.innerHTML = 'Hello World';",
    optionD: "document.getElement('p').innerHTML = 'Hello World';",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3: Which of the following is true about typeof operator in JavaScript?",
    optionA:
      "The typeof is a unary operator that is placed before its single operand, which can be of any type.",
    optionB: "value is a string indicating the data type of the operand.",
    optionC: "Both of the above.",
    optionD: "None of the above.",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4: Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?",
    optionA: "characterAt()",
    optionB: "getCharAt()",
    optionC: "charAt()",
    optionD: "None of the above.",
    answer: "C",
  },

  {
    question:
      "5: Which of the following function of Number object forces a number to display in exponential notation?",
    optionA: "toExponential()",
    optionB: "toFixed()",
    optionC: "toPrecision()",
    optionD: "toLocaleString()",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    question:
      "6: Which of the following function of Boolean object returns a string containing the source of the Boolean object?",
    optionA: "toSource()",
    optionB: "valueOf()",
    optionC: "toString()",
    optionD: "None of the above.",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7: Which of the following function of String object executes the search for a match between a regular expression and a specified string?",
    optionA: "concat()",
    optionB: "match()",
    optionC: "replace()",
    optionD: "search()",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    question:
      "8: Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case while respecting the current locale?",
    optionA: "toLocaleLowerCase()",
    optionB: "toLowerCase()",
    optionC: "toString()",
    optionD: "substring()",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    question:
      "9: Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed as a superscript, as if it were in a <sup> tag?",
    optionA: "sup()",
    optionB: "small()",
    optionC: "strike()",
    optionD: "sub()",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    question:
      "10: Which of the following function of Array object creates a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element in this array?",
    optionA: "push()",
    optionB: "join()",
    optionC: "pop()",
    optionD: "map()",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    question:
      "11: Which of the following function of Array object adds one or more elements to the front of an array and returns the new length of the array?",
    optionA: "sort()",
    optionB: "unshift()",
    optionC: "splice()",
    optionD: "toString()",
    answer: "B",
  },
];

export default QuestionList;
